Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/reneelindquist (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Teamwork
Microsoft Office
Self-starter

Languages

English Chinese

Renee Lindquist

Data Scientist

Orange County, California Area

Summary

Experienced Data Scientist with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Data Analysis, Statistical Modeling, SQL and other programming languages, Strong engineering professional with a Master's Degree focused in Applied Statistics from California State University-Long Beach.

Experience

Appriss
Data Scientist
July 2016 - Present (3 years 9 months)
Orange County, California Area

The Princeton Review
SAT Instructor
January 2015 - July 2016 (1 year 7 months)
Orange County, California Area

Created lesson plans suitable to the needs of the current class. Communicated abstract and difficult concepts effectively and in an easily understood and engaging manner.

Hillary for America NV Fellow June 2015 - August 2015 (3 months)

Recruit, train, and manage volunteers and activists. Participate in committee meetings and conferences. Monitor campaign activities closely in collaboration with Field Organizers and Regional Organizing Directors to ensure campaign goals.

UC Berkeley Intramural Sports Referee January 2011 - April 2013 (2 years 4 months) Berkeley, CA

Basketball Referee

Knott's Berry Farm Game Attendant June 2010 - August 2010 (3 months) Anaheim, CA

Explained the rules of the game to the guest and demonstrated how the game is played. Accurately balanced cash receipts and handled hundreds of dollars daily in a fast-paced environment. Provided personable and efficient customer service to a diverse clientele

Education

University of California, Berkeley
Bachelor's Degree, Applied Mathematics and Economics · (2010 - 2014)

California State University-Long Beach Master's Degree, Applied Statistics · (2015 - 2017)

Marina High School (2006 - 2010)